A Guide to the Papers of Collins Denny 1872-1943
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Collins Denny Correspondence
  - 1911-1922
    - H. L. Read to Collins Denny 1912 June 19-1926 August 21 (Box-folder 36:18)
    - G. C. Rector to Collins Denny 1918 July 6-1918 October 24 (Box-folder 36:19)
    - J. D. Redd to Collins Denny 1918 May 22-1925 December 9 (Box-folder 36:20)
    - Frank Reedy to Collins Denny 1913 January 14-1925 October 17 (Box-folder 36:21)
    - C. F. Reid to Collins Denny 1912 August 12-1914 November 9 (Box-folder 36:22)
    - Wm. O. Rencher to Collins Denny 1914 November 7-1919 October 23 (Box-folder 36:23)
    - Paul Renshaw to Collins Denny 1921 July 21-1938 May 18 (Box-folder 36:24)
    - J. H. Reynolds to Collins Denny 1920 May 31-1922 July 31 (Box-folder 36:25)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ra-Rh 1911-1922 (Box-folder 36:26)
    - F. M. Richardson to Collins Denny 1921 May 6-1937 November 9 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - G. W. Richardson to Collins Denny 1913 December 30-1932 February 26 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - G. L. Roberts to Collins Denny 1916 January 8-1926 March 27 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - J. S. Robertson to Collins Denny 1912 July 13-1917 October 5 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Leonidas Robinson to Collins Denny 1914 October 7-1921 March 9 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - F. A. Rogers to Collins Denny 1917 June 8-1918 January 12 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Daniel Roper to Collins Denny 1913 August 13-1933 March 20 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ri 1911-1922 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - J. C. Roper to Collins Denny 1914 January 23-1937 November 5 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Gilbert T. Rowe to Collins Denny 1921 July 9-1937 November 2 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ro 1911-1922 (Box-folder 37:11)
    - T. H. Ryan to Collins Denny 1921 January 11-1921 November 17 (Box-folder 37:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ru-Ry 1911-1922 (Box-folder 37:13)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 37:14)
    - Thomas Sanford to Collins Denny 1937 September 22-1912 August 25 (Box-folder 37:15)
    - Oliver Sands to Collins Denny 1920 February 5-1927 December 30 (Box-folder 37:16)
    - R. S. Satterfield to Collins Denny 1911 January 31-1922 April 10 (Box-folder 37:17)
    - J. E. Savage to Collins Denny 1911 February 26-1922 May 2 (Box-folder 37:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sa 1911-1922 (Box-folder 37:19)
    - John Score to Collins Denny 1912 December 21-1920 April 14 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sc 1911-1922 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Robert Selby to Collins Denny 1914 May 26-1916 May 13 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - C. C. Selecman to Collins Denny 1911 May 17-1939 December 15 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Se 1911-1922 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Edward F. Sheffey to Collins Denny 1914 January 1-1922 May 27 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - G. B. Sherman to Collins Denny 1919 June 20-1921 October 5 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - H. A. Sherman to Collins Denny 1911 September 25-1922 June 27 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - H. H. Sherman to Collins Denny 1913 February 3-1927 January 27 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - E. M. Shomborser to Collins Denny 1918 August 17-1922 July 26 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - H. R. Short to Collins Denny 1919 April 28-1921 September 27 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - F. H. Shuler to Collins Denny 1914 November 12-1922 August 5 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - T. C. Shuler to Collins Denny 1919 September 15-1922 May 10 (Box-folder 38:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sh 1911-1922 (Box-folder 38:14)
    - Jno. D. Simpson to Collins Denny 1915 January 12-1920 December 27 (Box-folder 38:15)
    - T. McN. Simpson to Collins Denny 1913 November 4-1920 May 14 (Box-folder 38:16)
    - S. T. Slaton to Collins Denny 1914 March 18-1916 October 27 (Box-folder 38:17)
    - D. P. Slaughter to Collins Denny 1916 May 22-1917 November 13 (Box-folder 38:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Si-Sl 1911-1922 (Box-folder 38:19)
    - W. Aiken Smart to Collins Denny 1913 December 10-1914 August 9 (Box-folder 38:20)
    - Bishop A. Frank Smith to Collins Denny 1914 March 27-1940 September 8 (Box-folder 38:21)
    - Levin Smith to Collins Denny 1916 January 10-1922 July 31 (Box-folder 38:22)
    - Rembert G. Smith to Collins Denny 1913 November 10-1920 April 27 (Box-folder 38:23)
    - R. N. Smith to Collins Denny 1918 September 21-1921 September 8 (Box-folder 38:24)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sma-Smy 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 38:25)
    - T. S. Southgate to Collins Denny 1917 November 19-1921 May 7 (Box-folder 38:26)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sn-So 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 38:27)
    - R. E. Stackhouse to Collins Denny 1913 January 1-1922 May 30 (Box-folder 39:1)
    - S. A. Steele to Collins Denny 1914 October 19-1920 September 15 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - J. R. Stewart to Collins Denny 1914 February 17-1916 February 12 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Albert A. Stone to Collins Denny 1912 August 13-1918 December 30 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - James A. Stone to Collins Denny 1921 April 21-1922 July 22 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Henry Stokes to Collins Denny 1914 May 26-1916 April 1 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Peter Stokes to Collins Denny 1914 November 2-1922 June 27 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - J. P. Strother to Collins Denny 1918 September 23-1920 August 16 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Charles M. Stuart to Collins Denny 1913 February 15-1920 February 7 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - George R. Stuart to Collins Denny 1913 July 12-1919 September 10 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - H. C. Stuart to Collins Denny 1913 November 14-1921 October 7 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - W. H. Stubblefield to Collins Denny 1912 September 29-1914 July 8 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - J. F. Sturdivant to Collins Denny 1914 June 23-1916 September 25 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sp-Sy 1911-1922 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Sp-Sy 1911-1922 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 39:16)
    - C. A. Tague to Collins Denny 1918 August 29-1921 January 24 (Box-folder 39:17)
    - R. M. Taylor to Collins Denny 1912 August 20-1913 April 8 (Box-folder 39:18)
    - W. B. Taylor to Collins Denny 1912 September 11-1920 February 20 (Box-folder 39:19)
    - George Teasley to Collins Denny 1916 May 18-1938 September 8 (Box-folder 39:20)
    - W. A. Tetley to Collins Denny 1911 March 8-1915 December 25 (Box-folder 39:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ta-Te 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 39:22)
    - Thomas & Thomas to Collins Denny 1917 July 25-1923 December 25 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Collins Thomas to Collins Denny 1913 February 7-1925 February 27 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Geo. W. Thompson to Collins Denny 1914 July 6-1915 April 1 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - S. J. Thompson to Collins Denny 1918 October 31-1921 July 25 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence: Th 1911-1922 (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Wilbur Tillet to Collins Denny 1912 October 30-1918 May 14 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Ezra Tipple to Collins Denny 1920 December 2-1922 April 18 (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Luther Todd to Collins Denny 1915 March 26-1922 April 5 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - W. E. Towson to Collins Denny 1921 September 11-1922 January 14 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ti-To 40:10 (Box-folder 40:10)
    - R. S. Truesdale to Collins Denny 1914 January 16-1922 July 26 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Frank A. Tyler to Collins Denny 1913 December 29-1921 July 7 (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Tr-Ty 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 40:13)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 40:14)
    - United Confederate Veterans to Collins Denny 1916 June 17-1919 November 26 (Box-folder 40:15)
    - S. B. Vaught to Collins Denny 1916 May 22-1921 May 7 (Box-folder 40:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence: U-V 1911-1922 (Box-folder 40:17)
    - Collins Denny Outgoing Correspondence; U-V 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 40:18)
    - T. J. Wade to Collins Denny 1920 January 7-1920 September 17 (Box-folder 40:19)
    - S. W. Walker to Collins Denny 1916 March 13-1921 July 13 (Box-folder 40:20)
    - J. B. Ward to Collins Denny 1913 May 13-1921 November 4 (Box-folder 40:21)
    - W. R. Ware to Collins Denny 1912 October 8-1922 June 23 (Box-folder 40:22)
    - A. F. Watkins to Collins Denny 1913 April 26-1922 July 29 (Box-folder 40:23)
    - E. O. Watson to Collins Denny 1913 February 1-1923 May 26 (Box-folder 40:24)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Wa 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 40:25)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1908-1915, excluding 1910-1911 (Box-folder 41:1)
      re: Vanderbilt case & University
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1910-1911 (Box-folder 41:2)
      re: Vanderbilt case
    - Vanderbilt University Quarterly, Vol. V, #4 1905 October (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Miscellaneous clippings n.d. (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Miscellaneous clippings n.d. (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Charles C. Weaver to Collins Denny 1912 October 11-1937 September 8 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Frank L. Wells to Collins Denny 1920 February 23-1922 April 11 (Box-folder 42:2)
    - P. B. Wells to Collins Denny 1912 October 30-1922 July 21 (Box-folder 42:3)
    - J. H. West to Collins Denny 1912 November 29-1922 June 5 (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; We 1911-1922 (Box-folder 42:5)
    - C. W. White to Collins Denny 1918 January 22-1918 April 22 (Box-folder 42:6)
    - G. Dorsey White to Collins Denny 1912 September 13-1916 December 22 (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Ben A. Whitmore to Collins Denny 1921 June 15-1937 October 12 (Box-folder 42:8)
    - S. P. Wissins to Collins Denny 1918 January 14-1922 June 15 (Box-folder 42:9)
    - Charles Williams to Collins Denny 1919 February 24-1919 November 10 (Box-folder 42:10)
    - O. F. Williams to Collins Denny 1915 January 11-1922 February 21 (Box-folder 42:11)
    - John O. Wilson to Collins Denny 1912 October 19-1922 May 20 (Box-folder 42:12)
    - J. B. Winn to Collins Denny 1913 August 30-1918 November 26 (Box-folder 42:13)
    - W. A. Winn to Collins Denny 1914 January 1-1918 June 8 (Box-folder 42:14)
    - W. U. White to Collins Denny 1911 January 27-1911 June 23 (Box-folder 42:15)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Wh-Wi 1911-1922 (Box-folder 42:16)
    - J. E. Wolfe to Collins Denny 1919 March 12-1922 March 17 (Box-folder 42:17)
    - Charles A. Wood to Collins Denny 1912 November 26-1913 March 20 (Box-folder 42:18)
    - E. L. Woolf to Collins Denny 1913 December 29-1921 February 18 (Box-folder 42:19)
    - W. H. Woolf to Collins Denny 1911 August 25-1913 July 23 (Box-folder 42:20)
    - Casper S. Wright to Collins Denny 1916 September 15-1920 July 3 (Box-folder 42:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Wo-Wy 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 42:22)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 42:23)
    - J. F. Yarbough to Collins Denny 1916 March 18-1938 May 11 (Box-folder 43:1)
    - W. J. Young to Collins Denny 1913 May 3-1922 January 10 (Box-folder 43:2)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; W, Y, & Z 1911- 1922 (Box-folder 43:3)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1911-1922 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - Petitions to Collins Denny 1910-1911 (Box-folder 43:5)
    - Petitions to Collins Denny 1912- 1914 (Box-folder 43:6)
    - Petitions to Collins Denny 1915- 1918 (Box-folder 43:7)
    - Petitions to Collins Denny 1919- 1922 (Box-folder 43:8)
    - Petitions to Collins Denny n.d. (Box-folder 43:9)
  - 1923- 1943
    - N. G. Augustus to Collins Denny 1935 November 2-1940 June 4 (Box-folder 44:1)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; A's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1923-1943 (Box-folder 44:3)
    - Jesse F. Benton to Collins Denny 1937 August 19-1937 September 8 (Box-folder 44:4)
    - Harry F. Byrd to Collins Denny 1937 June 2-1939 January 25 (Box-folder 44:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; B's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 44:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; B's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 44:7)
    - C. P. Chewning to Collins Denny 1939 January 21-1940 January 11 (Box-folder 44:8)
    - B. W. Crouch to Collins Denny 1937 July 15-1938 May 28 (Box-folder 44:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; C's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 44:10)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; C's 1922-1943 (Box-folder 44:11)
    - J. Lloyd Decell to Collins Denny 1925 March 16-1940 September 14 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - Charles Durant to Collins Denny 1937 May 22-1938 August 28 (Box-folder 44:13)
    - W. L. Duren to Collins Denny 1929 January 25-1937 September 2 (Box-folder 44:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; D's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 44:15)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; D's 1922-1943 (Box-folder 44:16)
    - H. C. Ewing to Collins Denny 1923 January 3-1925 October 3 (Box-folder 44:17')
    - W. D. Eye to Collins Denny 1926 June 3-1927 May 9 (Box-folder 44:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; E's 1935-1943 (Box-folder 44:19)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; E's 1922-1943 (Box-folder 44:20)
    - W. A. Fairy to Collins Denny 1922 October 24-1924 November 17 (Box-folder 45:1)
    - R. E. L. Farmer to Collins Denny 1924 November 24-1928 September 29 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - C. C. Featherstone to Collins Denny 1919 May 14-1937 May 21 (Box-folder 45:3)
    - James H. Felts to Collins Denny 1925 February 24-1930 November 25 (Box-folder 45:4)
    - B. A. Few to Collins Denny 1924 April 29-1926 February 11 (Box-folder 45:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1931- 1933 (Box-folder 45:6)
      re: Personal Finances
    - C. C. Fisher to Collins Denny 1918 June 21-1937 October 13 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - V. M. Fleming to Collins Denny 1917 September 5-1930 January 2 (Box-folder 45:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; F's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 45:9)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; F's 1922- 1943
    - A. F. Gearhead to Collins Denny 1929 May 21-1928 July 3 (Box-folder 45:11)
    - W. O. Goode to Collins Denny 1925 October 1-1922 May 31 (Box-folder 45:12)
    - James H. Green to Collins Denny 1922 October 16-1926 October 17 (Box-folder 45:13)
    - W. T. Green to Collins Denny 1926 May 24-1930 June 12 (Box-folder 45:14)
    - A. Gunter to Collins Denny 1922 August 20-1926 October 7 (Box-folder 45:15)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; G's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 45:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; G's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 45:17)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; G's 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 45:18)
    - O. L. Haga to Collins Denny 1926 April 24-1928 April 22 (Box-folder 45:19)
    - C. E. Hall to Collins Denny 1927 February 4-1929 November 9 (Box-folder 45:20)
    - J. A. Hall to Collins Denny 1925 March 30-1926 July 8 (Box-folder 45:21)
    - Leon M. Hall to Collins Denny 1924 August 25-1925 November 30 (Box-folder 45:22)
    - T. S. Hamilton to Collins Denny 1925 April 2-1929 August 19 (Box-folder 45:23)
    - L. Hammond to Collins Denny 1926 May 1-1927 March 13 (Box-folder 45:24)
    - W. S. Hammond to Collins Denny 1924 July 26-1927 April 12 (Box-folder 45:25)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ha-Han 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 45:26)
    - Noland B. Harmon to Collins Denny 1924 October 2-1937 May 15 (Box-folder 46:1)
    - F. S. Harmon to Collins Denny 1925 February 27-1932 March 30 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - Fred R. Harper to Collins Denny 1939 May 9-1939 August 14 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Costan J. Harrell to Collins Denny 1925 August 18-1940 September 3 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Fairfax Harrison to Collins Denny 1928 June 12-1933 December 28 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - L. O. Hartman to Collins Denny 1937 October 13-1938 July 7 (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Har 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Henry G. Hawkins to Collins Denny 1930 May 28-1932 August 31 (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Zack Hayes to Collins Denny 1937 July 27-1938 June 21 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Hat-Hay 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 46:10)
    - H. B. Henry to Collins Denny 1924 August 28-1927 September 3 (Box-folder 46:11)
    - C. C. Herbert to Collins Denny 1922 May 11-1925 October 6 (Box-folder 46:12)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; He 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 46:13)
    - R. H. Hiner to Collins Denny 1927 September 14-1929 October 14 (Box-folder 46:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 46:15)
      re: Historical Commissions
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Hi 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 46:16)
    - H. L. Hoffman to Collins Denny 1923 November 5-1928 September 20 (Box-folder 46:17)
    - A. E. Holler to Collins Denny 1922 May 16-1925 October 28 (Box-folder 46:18)
    - C. L. Hornaday to Collins Denny 1923 March 29-1925 October 19 (Box-folder 46:19)
    - R. S. Howie to Collins Denny 1922 September 5-1924 July 10 (Box-folder 46:20)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ho's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Bishop Edwin Hughes to Collins Denny 1938 December 23-1942 March 16 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - H. A. Humble to Collins Denny 1925 December 23-1942 March 16 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - C. W. Hunt to Collins Denny 1923 June 13-1931 July 13 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - W. L. Hutchins to Collins Denny 1923 August 1-1925 October 5 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Hu-Hy 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; H's 1922-1943 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - Illinois Central Railroad to Collins Denny 1923 August 1-1931 February 3 (Box-folder 47:8)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; I's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; I's 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ja-Je 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 47:11)
    - James A. Johnson to Collins Denny 1927 January 6-1928 July 11 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - Wade Johnson to Collins Denny 1925 August 11-1929 September 20 (Box-folder 47:13)
    - E. Ruffins Jones to Collins Denny 1925 June 27-1930 May 23 (Box-folder 47:14)
    - E. S. Jones to Collins Denny 1922 August 10-1926 January 16 (Box-folder 47:15)
    - Geo. A. Jones to Collins Denny 1937 June 28-1937 November 27 (Box-folder 47:16)
    - Geo. W. Jones to Collins Denny 1924 June 28-1929 October 9 (Box-folder 47:17)
    - Roscoe Jones to Collins Denny 1924 October 8-1928 September 10 (Box-folder 47:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Jo's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 47:19)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; J's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 47:20)
    - T. C. Keeling to Collins Denny 1937 August 25-1938 April 9 (Box-folder 48:1)
    - E. L. Kirk to Collins Denny 1922 August 14-1925 September 19 (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Wm. L. Knight to Collins Denny 1924 May 25-1937 May 26 (Box-folder 48:3)
    - John Knox to Collins Denny 1928 January 14-1938 March 22 (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; K's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; K's 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 48:6)
    - J. R. Laird to Collins Denny 1922 June 2-1940 January 16 (Box-folder 48:7)
    - A. S. Lamar to Collins Denny 1903 August 24-1922 October 30 (Box-folder 48:8)
    - A. S. Lamar to Collins Denny 1923 January 1-1933 April 20 (Box-folder 48:9)
    - Theodore Law to Collins Denny 1924 February 21-1926 December 2 (Box-folder 48:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; La 1923-1943 (Box-folder 48:11)
    - Bishop F. D. Leete to Collins Denny 1938 December 16-1940 October 1 (Box-folder 48:12)
    - Geo. C. Leonard to Collins Denny 1922 August 12-1924 October 19 (Box-folder 48:13)
    - L. M. Lipscombe to Collins Denny 1924 July 16-1930 December 5 (Box-folder 48:14)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Le-Li 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 48:15)
    - F. S. Love to Collins Denny 1915 November 2-1925 July 28 (Box-folder 48:16)
    - J. F. Lupo to Collins Denny 1923 March 8-1924 March 26 (Box-folder 48:17)
    - F. A. Lupton to Collins Denny 1922 August 9-1923 August 28 (Box-folder 48:18)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Lo-Ly 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 48:19)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; L 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 48:20)
    - M. W. Mann to Collins Denny 1923 May 18-1925 October 13 (Box-folder 49:1)
    - J. T. Mangum to Collins Denny 1922 August 23-1923 November 1 (Box-folder 49:2)
    - L. A. Manning to Collins Denny 1924 November 26-1942 August 21 (Box-folder 49:3)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ma's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 49:4)
    - J. T. McClure to Collins Denny 1926 April 2-1931 September 25 (Box-folder 49:5)
    - E. L. McCoy to Collins Denny 1922 November 16-1925 October 12 (Box-folder 49:6)
    - L. P. M. McGee to Collins Denny 1922 May 29-1930 August 22 (Box-folder 49:7)
    - Wm. A. McKee to Collins Denny 1926 October 14-1928 August 21 (Box-folder 49:8)
    - E. McWhorter to Collins Denny 1922 October 20-1929 June 11 (Box-folder 49:9)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mc's 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 49:10)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Me 1923-1943 (Box-folder 49:11)
    - A. C. Millar to Collins Denny 1924 May 3-1931 September 3 (Box-folder 49:12)
    - O. B. Mitchell to Collins Denny 1924 July 21-1924 November 19 (Box-folder 49:13)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mi 1923- 1943 (Box-folder 49:14)
    - A. H. Mohn to Collins Denny 1924 February 27-1925 April 10 (Box-folder 49:15)
    - A. J. Montague to Collins Denny 1916 March 18-1927 January 3 (Box-folder 49:16)
    - J. H. Montgomery to Collins Denny 1923 January 3-1926 December 3 (Box-folder 49:17)
    - Bishop Arthur Moore to Collins Denny 1929 May 17-1942 December 18 (Box-folder 49:18)
    - James T. Moore to Collins Denny 1926 October 26-1931 August 1 (Box-folder 49:19)
    - G. L. Morelock to Collins Denny 1922 November 2-1928 February 11 (Box-folder 49:20)
    - T. E. Morris to Collins Denny 1924 November 22-1925 March 28 (Box-folder 49:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mo's 1923-1942 (Box-folder 49:22)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Mu-My 1923-1943 (Box-folder 50:1)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; M's 1922-1943 (Box-folder 50:2)
    - Near East College Association to Collins Denny 1927 December 19-1928 March 2 (Box-folder 50:3)
    - W. J. Nelms to Collins Denny 1927 June 28-1928 November 3 (Box-folder 50:4)
    - W. H. Nelson to Collins Denny 1924 June 6-1938 March 11 (Box-folder 50:5)
    - E. D. Newman to Collins Denny 1926 January 5-1927 April 23 (Box-folder 50:6)
    - Ralph E. Nollner to Collins Denny 1925 April 4-1937 October 16 (Box-folder 50:7)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; N's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 50:8)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence 1922-1943 (Box-folder 50:9)
    - G. G. Oliver to Collins Denny 1923 March 14-1928 October 2 (Box-folder 50:10)
    - T. J. O'Neil to Collins Denny 1930 August 16-1933 October 33 (Box-folder 50:11)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; O's 1923-1943 (Box-folder 50:12)
    - Collins Denny Sr. Outgoing Correspondence; O's 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 50:13)
    - Cordie Page to Collins Denny 1925 May 13-1925 November 27 (Box-folder 50:14)
    - A. J. Parker to Collins Denny 1923 September 1-1925 October 26 (Box-folder 50:15)
    - Franklin N. Parker to Collins Denny 1925 May 11-1931 August 26 (Box-folder 50:16)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Pa 1922- 1939 (Box-folder 50:17)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Pe 1922- 1943 (Box-folder 50:18)
    - H. L. Phifer to Collins Denny 1924 December 13-1937 November 5 (Box-folder 50:19)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Ph 1922- 1934 (Box-folder 50:20)
    - Wm. B. Pistole to Collins Denny 1933 August 27-1937 September 11 (Box-folder 50:21)
    - Collins Denny Correspondence; Pi 1922-1943 (Box-folder 50:22)
    - Jno. G. Pollard to Collins Denny 1930 February 6-1931 November 9 (Box-folder 50:23)
    - J. A. Porter to Collins Denny 1924 February 6-1930 August 18 (Box-folder 50:24)
    - Otto Porter to Collins Denny 1930 December 27-1937 December 17 (Box-folder 50:25)